ISLAM **KAMILOV**

12430 Oxford Park Dr. Apt 521, Houston, TX 77082 | C: 832-407-1152 | kamilov6@gmail.com

Professional Summary

Motivated to build software program and experienced working with groups. Dedicated to learning and improving programs. Background in software development and cyber security.

Core Qualifications

Java; Bash; C; JavaScript; HTML/CSS; Swift; MySQL; PHP; ASP .NET;

Projects:

- **Study Learn Teach** (2016). Created website online exams and learned topics for elementary, middle, and high school students using *JavaScript and HTML/CSS*.
- **CPU Scheduling Algorithms** (2016). Created a graphic interface program FCFS, SJN, SRT, RR and EDF algorithms simulated cycle-by-cycle using *Java*.
- **Balancing Robot Project** (2015). Created a two wheel robots which could balance it self when moving around using *Arduino*.

Experience

Conversation Partner North American University

02/2017 to Present Houston, TX

- Provide instruction to students in public speaking and communication
- Discussing new topics

Software Engineering Mentor Berkeley Research Group LLC

01/2016 to 06/2016 Houston, TX

- Setup a Cyber Security Data Sharing Program
- Understanding STIX and TAXII
- Using STIX and TAXII to automate how cyber threat information shared

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science: Software Engineering

May 2018

North American University

Houston, TX

GPA: 3.73/4.00

Fellowships and Awards

1st place at 6th Annual Texas Security Awareness Week (TexSAW). *UT Dallas*, 2016 *Gold Medal* at International Young Inventors Project Olympiad. *Georgia*, *Tbilisi*, 2013 1st place at Mathematical Olympiad. *Kyrgyzstan*, state Osh, 2011 Organizer at 1st Annual Moonlight CTF at North American University, *Houston*, 2016

Professional Affiliations

ACM Club, Member, 2015

Cyber Security Club, Member, 2016

Web Development Club, Member, 2015

NAU International Cultural Festival, Kyrgyzstan Representative, 2014 - 2015